Ah, nice.
ああ、いいねー
As a piece.
ピースとして
Shall we go to bed?
ベッドに行こうか
Let's go to bed for once.
一回ベッドに行こう
Let's go to bed.
ベ ッドに行こう
Lie here.
ここ寝転んで
Lie down.
寝転んで
Well then, fill it in a little more.
じゃあさ、 もうちょっと、 ちょっと入れつぶせ
It's a little bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of.
入れるのは、 入れるのは、 ちょっと さすがに
why?
なんで?
If you get this far, let me in.
ここまで来たら入れさせて
It's a bit obvious to include it.
入れるのは、ちょっとさすがに
Why why?
なんでなんで?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
That's good.
いい じゃん
Well, that's true, but
まあ、そうだけど、
Let's each other, let's each other,
お 互いさ、 お互いはなかだしてさ、
It makes me want to sleep.
寝たくなるじゃん
My voice was coming out.
声出てたし
Well then, should I add some money?
じゃあさ、 お金プラスしたらいい?
Also.
また
Talking rubber.
喋ってゴム
Does that mean I should wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいいってこと?
No, it's actually a little raw.
いや、 生はさすがにちょっと
Yeah.
うん
Does that mean I should wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいいってこと?
So, which is better, rubber or raw?
じゃあ、ゴムか生どっちがいい?
It's rubber.
それはゴム
Rubber?
ゴム?
Does that mean I can put it in if I put on a rubber band?
ゴムつけたら入れていいってこと?
I'll make it shorter.
時間短めにするから
So it's petit, right?
だったらプチでしょ?
I'll save you time.
時間プチにするから
Wouldn't that be fine?
だったらいいっしょ?
It's because I'm saving my time.
時間プチにするんだからさ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
You'll make more money too.
お金も増やすんだ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
I'll put it in then.
じゃあ入れるよ
rubber.
ゴム
Should I wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいい?
So I put on the rubber.
じゃあゴムつけたよ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってて
I said okay.
いいって言ったもんね
Can I put it on?
つけれる?
Have you ever worn it?
つけたことある?
It doesn't work at all.
全然つかないじゃん
endure, endure.
耐える耐える
If only it didn't last this long.
こんなにつかなかったら
No.
ダメだよ
It's gone bad.
ダメになったじゃん
I won't wear this.
これつけないよ
You won't wear it.
つけないでしょ
Make it raw?
生にする?
No?
ダメ?
I got another one.
もう1個取ってきた
Before applying it, squeeze it firmly with your hands.
つける前に手でしごいてガッチリして
Even rubber is fine.
ゴムだっていいんだよね
Because I put it on.
つ けたから
Because I said okay.
いいって言ったからね
I told you to put on a rubber band.
ゴムつけたらいいって言ったからね
It's on.
ついてるよ
what up?
どうした?
Suddenly.
急 に
what up?
どうした?
It's on, right?
ついてるでしょ
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
It feels good, so it's okay.
気持ちいいからいいでしょ
You're getting louder than before.
さっきより声出てるでしょ
Get on your elbows.
ひじついて
You're getting louder than before.
さっきより声出てるでしょ
Lean only your upper body.
上半身だけ倒して
Next, put it in from the top.
次に上から入れてくんね
Put it in from above.
上から入れて
From lying down.
寝転んから
Come on up.
上に来て
Please wake me up.
よく起こして
Grind or something.
グラインドとかして
Touch me.
あちくべとか触ってよ
Raise your foot once.
一回足あげて
Put your hand between my legs.
手を俺の足の間に入れる
Leave it here.
これで置いて
Push me.
押さって
Because it's been a while.
もう久々するから
Can I try it again?
もう一回やっていい?
Are you going to do it again?
もう一回やるんですか?
Because it's a plus.
プラスするから
I just don't have it on hand right now.
今ちょっと手持ちつかないけどさ
I'll take it down later.
あとで下ろすからさ
Just take this for now.
とりあえずこれだけ取って
good?
いい?
Shall we do it again?
もう一回やる?
Okay.
いいよ
Not once, not twice.
もう一回も二回もね
There's no text.
文もないし
Yeah.
うん
Because it's the second shot.
2発目だからさ